OK, perfect. So um,
I was keep working on this. Um.
Let me show you what I gave you,
what I did, what I have done.
I migrate our project to React.
So now we are using React nor JavaScript
or like HTML anymore.
So we are using React because here I can.
Mhm. Yeah.
And one of the things that you told me is
that you need consistency for your demo,
Connect.
right?
So I I created a small database with with
a note package and I created all of these
items are like.
100% data.
Now I try to replicate data as much as
Oh, cool.
possible so I can change.
Uh huh.
You asked system to generate the data,
right?
Exactly. For example,
here is a JSON with the search attributes,
for example here, right and here.
Mhm.
There you go.
I can maybe I can send you this so you
can review it if it's fine.
For example a shipment of order details,
Mhm, mhm.
right?
Shipment. Yeah. If you OK, I can. Yeah.
Shipment order details, yeah.
And.
As order details.
Yeah, this is on the say.
There are two type of shipments, right?
One is a buy and the other one is a sell,
right?
Exactly this is.
On the buy side you have load mapping.
Load mapping is very similar to the that
of the order. That's fine.
OK, uh, maybe it's here. I don't know. So.
Would you think it will look better if I
have sorry inside of order details I I
will need to have the a buy a buy what
would you call it buy shipment and sell
shipment right?
Yeah,
maybe I will send you one sample by
shipment out and sell shipment out by in.
OK, I will say I will give you sample.
Uh huh.
Right.
I'll put it in this chat so that he can
use it.
So you can see what type of shipments are
these. I'm attaching a Jason file.
The chat, right?
Yeah.
OK.
No, I see.
So buy out is a buy side and sell out is
a sell side.
So that is a real looking data like
structure. Oh, perfect. I will, I will,
Correct. Yeah.
I will work on that then. OK, so here is,
yeah. And then you have a lot of them.
You see, I have a lot of shipments here.
Hmm.
And then I also have this other one.
Here it is. You see it's by shipment,
Yeah.
see sell shipment.
Yeah, correct.
But this is not because inside by
shipping you have a lot of things, right?
Inside starship and you have a lot of
things as well, right?
Correct. Yeah.
But then I have to correct this. OK,
so let's go back to the demo. And yeah,
we we do the same thing as before.
Let's review the things that oh,
first let me show you here.
I implemented the tool tip, you remember.
Two. Yeah, two orders, 4 orders.
Fantastic. Cool. It's now showing, yeah.
OK.
Then we have the export as well,
export all records or if we are filtering
for example, let's say 43.
So we have 13 items.
So if we put export we'll just try to
export 13 records.
Yeah.
13 item all filtered records export all
records. All records is like 200 records.
What do you mean by see the filtering all
records?
What I was asking was there are two
filtering right?
Huh.
One is you are allowing the user to only
download what they have filtered.
Right, what I mean as all records.
Instead of all records,
it should be all columns, right?
I probably have it as.
Do I have it as records in PPT?
Let me see.
It thinks, well, here is the.
Uh.
Fields. I say current fields, right?
Current fields are all fields.
What I meant by all fields is columns.
Do you want to say for the same you
Um.
filtered only 13 records right?
For the records,
do you want to download only the columns
that you have set?
Set on the table or do you want all the
42 fields to be downloaded records for
the 42 fields to be downloaded for the 13
records?
Yeah.
OK, OK. So the export will be limited,
but by in in both cases by no. OK, but.
13 Yeah,
in both cases it will be limited to 13
records, right?
But the first one export all records you
will you will say you know that the table
has 42 columns, correct?
I know.
Yeah,
but there are only like 15 or 20 columns
right now because that's what the user
selected.
Hmm.
Right.
If we if the user clicks export all
Yeah.
records, it'll for the 13 records,
it'll download the information related to
42 columns.
Oh, OK. And when?
Say there could be tracking messages,
but they are not interested in tracking
messages.
They they they could be like for example
ship tendering status, right?
It might not be showing in the table,
but it's behind the scene.
It is an information for that record for
Yeah.
that shipment.
I see I understand now.
So when you say all,
it will export all of the columns, right?
Exactly all records, not all records.
That's why all fields I wrote it.
OK.
I wrote as a whole fields.
You can make it as all columns, right?
That's what the one Kathleen was.
Kathleen and I were discussing.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah, I I I remember. OK.
Yeah, so export all columns, right?
Then it'll export all the columns for
Uh.
that record 13 records.
And what if you didn't filter anything
which is showing all of the items?
200 items, yeah,
200 items will get downloaded and then
OK.
it'll be all columns or only the ones
that you are viewing.
Oh, OK, perfect. And the limit is 10,000,
right? 10,000 records, OK.
10,000.
Yeah.
Oh, great. Perfect.
That's that's something.
Instead of asking the user saying like do
you want to refine your search,
just let them say like OK,
just download 1st 10,000 records right?
Then we can refine it.
This is just an idea right?
What how the it would work so it'll be a
better for the for them to tell how it's
expected to work. That's all.
OK.
It doesn't have to be perfect.
For now you can leave it as it is,
but you could just change it into all
fields or you know you just go to
download 200 records.
But it's all fields are just right,
only selected the ones that you are
viewing columns.
However you want to name it,
either the columns or you want to name it
OK.
as fields. That is the.
Up to you.
Mm.
So maybe I I was thinking about something
now.
Maybe when you selected the the the ones,
the columns that are shown,
maybe you want to have a a little brief
or what are those columns here?
Down here, maybe let's say this.
No, that is already there in the setting,
right? If you go to the setting,
Um, these actions.
if you close this.
Instead of having 200 records,
you need to say 13 records and if you go
Um.
to that setting next to that export
export,
what is that one next to that export?
Um.
Next, next to that, their first icon.
First icon, yeah.
OK, no this is and this is not working.
This is for I think the arrangement of.
If you click on that.
OK, say if you open my PPT, right?
If you open my PPT, then if you go to.
OK.
Uh-huh.
Why is it closed? It was closed.
There you go.
Uh, it's the first one, right?
Right. It's the first one exactly.
Just a second.
OK.
Here it is.
Oh.
Can you can you see my screen?
No, I cannot. Yeah, it's coming up now.
Yeah.
OK.
Yeah, if you see there,
there is a change view, right #4.
Mhm.
Right if you go to sheet number page #4.
Yeah, where I remember the the columns.
Right,
so these are the all the columns which
are present right?
The last one that that option is that the
Mm.
user knows that they would.
You need to add that as well, right?
So you need to give them give the user
saying that this functionality they
should be able to change the.
Number of columns and then we can go to
export right?
So that in that way when we give the demo
they understand saying that oh this is
these are all the fields columns that
they will be able to manage and when you
export either only the ones that you are
viewing is going to come out or it's all
of the fields for the filtered results
you're going to get it.
Because what I was thinking is when when
you're a user that is that has like let's
say this is 3/6, let's say 15 columns.
There is a user that is seeing a 15
Mhm.
columns.
Most of those columns will be hitting
right here, right?
To the left.
It'll you'll have a scroll bar, right?
Bottom scroll.
There you go. Yeah, something like that,
you see.
Yeah, so you have a scroll.
I don't see the scroll.
Exactly so.
Can you see my screen? It's just crawling.
I can see your screen. You are scrolling,
but do you have a scrollbar?
I don't see a scrollbar.
Yeah, we can put it here maybe.
You I uh, you can put it there,
or you can put it on the top, right?
Wherever it suits.
So what I what I meant is the user is
going to forget it has so many columns.
That is why I was telling you maybe we
should before exporting we should remind
him.
Hey, you have 15 columns, whatever,
and those columns are this, this, this,
this, this.
Yeah, the for prototyping.
I think that's fine right for just giving
demo.
But as we think about it right as we go
to the exact requirement,
I I have not seen those kind of things
show, but they would understand, right?
Say for example,
this feature is available in JIRA as well.
Right. If you go to JIRA,
they don't give you all that information.
Uh huh.
They will just say like, OK,
because it's kind of very simple to do.
Probably I don't have anything open right
now.
I can't make Jira here.
Pam Chira open OK if you go to.
Where should I go to?
Go to the three dots to the right,
but you should have a table somewhere you
need to go. One second,
you need to export to Excel, right?
Go export to Excel.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, right.
See all the fields. Fields.
Just click on fields. Export. Yeah,
export.
Even if you see here, they might.
If you actually go to some kind of an,
you know,
what is that epic board or something,
OK.
you might be able to see maybe if you
open that Excel.
You see automatically they downloaded all
the columns, right? You see that?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, yeah, of course it's a lot.
Here is auto variation.
Yeah,
normally they would give you an option.
Do you want to during the download
process,
they will give you an option whether do
you want to download all the columns or
you just wanted to download the ones that
you're viewing.
Mm.
Right,
so it downloaded everything relevant to
But.
in the detail section.
Then all the items in here,
whatever headers you have,
everything it downloaded.
OK,
but that that that should show in a in a
table, right?
Is there a table in Odyssey one?
Yeah, there is a table. If you go to OK,
if you go to timeline, timeline,
go to timeline, timeline,
second next to the summary, same. Yeah,
Oh.
timeline, right. So if you look here,
this is a kind of a table.
It lists you all the.
Um, list of epics, right? If you go there,
yeah, export right? Spreadsheet, right?
Did it directly download? Yeah,
it didn't give you any option.
OK, it didn't gave me a.
Normally it gives you option saying like
OK how you want to download it.
And maybe here, maybe here.
Active Sprint.
Mm.
Go to forms, forms or list. Go to list,
list, list, list. Yeah,
list right now it is in a list.
Now try to if you try to download it.
Mhm.
You do not view as chat. Yeah,
go to the top Odyssey one board right
next to that Odyssey one board.
Oh.
Odyssey one board. There are three dots,
right? OK, it is not coming.
Let's see.
Let me see. I can show you,
but you got the idea right?
It it tells you in the certain way.
Exactly. Yeah, I got idea. Got idea. OK,
OK, it's fine.
You should be here, right? It's weird.
Yeah, it is. It is somewhere there.
That's why I'm also trying to figure out
that one is.
Maybe here our settings,
do it here export.
Export.
OK, let's keep going.
Yeah.
OK,
so here will be your column arrangement
panel. It will look like this.
I I need to.
I still need to construct this part which
is the same one as the one in the bottom.
Uh then.
Oh, you have it here. Column adjustment.
OK, you have it on the right side. OK,
Let's go to.
yeah.
In the column.
No, no, no, no, your this one.
I did see your what is that your design
that you showed for column, right?
Oh, OK. Yeah.
Yeah,
here we're gonna do a column arrangement
for the table, right?
So it will look like this instead of this
small one that I show you at the
beginning.
Right, right.
So we use this component for filtering
and also for arrangements.
For example here is the filtering.
So this is the query saved and this is
working as well. But I don't want to.
I don't want to get into much filtering
yet because I need a better data.
Correct.
So with your that you send me,
we can improve it.
Yeah, we can see we are,
we can tell them saying that we are
working on that particular idea.
It could be natural language or it could
be something different, right?
So that that also we can say we don't
Yeah, sure.
have to tell them exactly saying like how
it works, it's just an idea, right?
OK, perfect.
And then if we select a shipment that you
saw it as before,
here we can select the order.
Yeah.
So this shipment that I selected is this
is very nice.
It is auto scrolls for you so you can see
which one do you selected.
Correct.
Here this one has four, right?
So here I can select each one.
Right.
David told me something that was
interesting. So David told me,
Fantastic. It looks cool, yeah.
gave me a feedback about this, he said.
Maybe users are not gonna remember like
the difference between this and this.
They will probably remember the.
I don't know the some attribute of from
the order.
Yeah, it is attribute of the order.
You know.
Yeah, it is order details, right?
Yeah, for.
Exactly.
So maybe he said maybe we can put here
and where does it come from?
Order blah blah blah comes from Wyoming,
whatever.
So the user understands which one is
which you know.
Something like that.
But.
At IF Alaba.
But whatever you selected is order, right?
Exactly. This is an order.
Yeah,
and it you have shipped from and shipped
to, right? That makes sense, correct?
Yeah.
It's from here.
Yeah,
I don't know what improvement there is
required.
I thought like it was clearly
communicating.
Oh oh,
because he said maybe the user doesn't
understand this, this, this code,
this order number.
He he's he was saying that maybe you
shouldn't put the order number name here.
Maybe you should put something else.
So the user understands what is this
order about. Yeah,
but at the same time you have all this to
understand what is this about.
Yeah, correct. I don't,
I don't understand the point,
but say when once you select and you go
to product, right, how does it go? OK,
Sure.
if you go to product, OK,
displays all the product. Cool, that's it.
Yeah, displace all.
It's all single line.
There is no this one. Yeah,
it has two lines and then it displays the.
That's it. You got it.
Uh.
Yeah, as a default, we can explain. Yeah,
that's fine.
And then if we go, oh, and this is nice,
I I forgot to show you. We go to order,
we can scroll here as well.
So if it hides.
Hmm.
And then here we can close it,
maybe open it again.
And here we have the arrangement as well,
right?
What is that arrangement?
And the column arrangement for this.
Oh, column arrangement. OK, OK, OK, yeah,
that is not column, right?
And.
It is tab arrangements, correct? Oh,
column arrangements for the OK,
Oh yeah, exactly.
column arrangements for what?
For the product?
No,
I was thinking about these because in in
Tab arrangements, right?
your power, yeah,
in your PowerPoint you pointed this ones,
right? This ones.
Yeah,
these are configurations for the tabs,
right? Tabs for the bottom screen,
correct?
Exactly. Uh, so where we were? OK.
So let's go to routing guide.
Right.
So it says let's put the accepted ones
below because this is the logic of this
is like hey if we got declined and versus
when you you get declined right or
Yeah.
rejected sorry.
Correct, correct, correct.
And then accepted or then declined
because declined means you you are now an
exception, right?
Or what it means or is true?
Yeah,
decline means decline means you sent the
tender out, but uh,
they did not accept it.
None of them, right? Accepted, OK.
Yeah,
the first one declined means see rejected
as they rejected as rejected.
Rejected means it timed out, right?
Oh, OK, so it didn't.
It couldn't find anything.
Yeah, it could not find.
They didn't respond within that time.
OK, and the client is.
And I I just.
The client is like they the carrier said
that I cannot take this load.
OK.
And for and for this routing and and for
this routing guide right if you go to the
So you you can be declined.
Uh.
second PPD that I sent.
Yeah.
Right. Second PPT, not the first one.
Second.
Where is your?
Did I close it?
Yeah, this is the one.
Yeah,
you need to get get it in this particular
order, right? If you go to tender,
if you go to the fourth page, right?
Yes, mhm.
If you see here,
it needs to have different tabs,
pod top section will be there and then if
you go back to your screen,
if you go back to your this one,
is it just?
Routing options.
Um.
Was it just routing options?
Now go to your bottom part.
Bottom one.
Oh OK routing guide right?
So it says routing guide.
Uh.
Should we want to have routing guide or
tender screen?
I would say instead of calling it as
routing guide,
you might have to call it as tender
tender screen tender.
Huh.
Enter screen OK.
Yeah, tender screen this.
This should be there, right?
This entire section should be there.
Oh, which one this this?
This bottom section, yeah.
This one.
Shipment order, pickup, final delivery.
If then, oh, all of this, OK.
All of this,
all of this will come inside that
particular thing.
Oh, I see.
OK, I think um.
This is 1 has rate direct cost,
but if this is not the same.
Maybe what you can do is right,
you can leave the routing.
Don't work on this one.
Make the tender page separate right so
that you know you can work on it and you
can say link it to this one and say that
this is the tender page.
Maybe it's this one gender history or not.
Right.
Tender history is how do you say that you
would have sent out to some set of
carriers and then the customer might have
Um.
added an order or might have added
something to that shipment and then.
The complete routing changed, right?
The first option,
the set of first carriers generated was
not the same as the second set of jet
Yeah.
carrier generated because there was a new
order that was added in or there was a
new stop that came in or there was a
origin that changed.
Right.
That is when you retender to a different
Mm.
set of carriers, right? There is a rank.
If you see here,
Mhm.
there is a set of rank and there are
certain selection of carriers that it is
made for initial tender.
That entire process is scrapped and then
a new process is started again to
identify the carrier and then.
Retender to those carriers.
It becomes the old one.
The first one becomes a history.
OK, OK,
so the first one becomes as a history
Right.
part,
as a history part as a tender history. OK,
Correct gender history.
OK, so.
But if you do the routing guide tender
history, we can come back, right?
It's going to be simpler version of that.
It's not going to be a complex version,
Yeah.
right?
Routing guide is instead of calling
OK.
routing guide,
you just call it as tendering.
Entering. OK, perfect.
So that that is that is good to know.
Yeah.
So let's go to cost allocation this one.
Well,
we need to discuss on this one first.
Let's go to the easier ones, OK.
Instructions.
I think the only thing that I added here
Yeah.
is this type of instructions, right?
Because when you create instructions in
the orders domain,
you select which ones do you want to show.
Exactly. Yeah,
that's that's the correct one, right.
Right. So it's OK. History.
History is different from tender history,
right?
No, both are same. History and tendency.
You can eliminate. Yeah, eliminate one.
Both are insane.
You can eliminate history, yeah.
OK, OK, perfect.
And then upload the documents.
There you go. You can upload it.
David told me another.
Oh, 111 second. One second.
The history is the overall changes made
to the shipment. Yeah, let it be there,
right? Say for example,
if a quantity changed, right?
If a shipment on a shipment level,
Oh, OK.
if something changed, it's like.
What do you say?
If shipment weight gross weight changed
from 8000 lbs to 9000 lbs,
that'll be in shipment history, right?
Then if the if there were initially 2
orders and then one more order was added
to that shipment,
then it'll be in history.
It is for the shipment history, right?
But tender history is for that particular
set of routing options.
What happened right?
If you generate a new set of routing
options,
Mhm.
the first one becomes a first becomes a
tender history and then the second one,
third one, you can generate many more.
Gender histories right based on how many
routing options you're creating.
Mm-hmm. I gotcha. OK.
So history you can do it like Jira if you
open Jira, right?
Um.
He's got to Jira.
Yeah, I just go to JIRA. You can.
The idea behind that is just the same,
right? If you, yeah,
if you open any story,
go to go to the second one 7559.
You will. OK, yeah, open any story.
That's fine.
Yeah, if you come to the bottom.
Scroll down, Scroll down, Scroll down.
Keep scrolling.
Mhm.
Right. Yeah. If you stop here,
if you go to history,
if you click on history, if you go up,
go up, go.
Yeah.
Go up right there history right?
Then you can see this person assigned it
to Mangesh, right?
Kathleen assigned it to say you can see
Oh.
change to assign,
assign change to Niranjana.
So it is like capturing the.
Date,
time and what happened at that moment?
OK.
Right, so that is why if you go to my PPT,
it'll give you examples like date,
OK.
time and what what exactly changed at the
it's first PPT.
Date time. Where is that?
Yeah, yeah, you come down, come down,
keep coming down.
I don't think you created a tender
history.
I think instruction, document,
internal notes, routing option.
I not create.
I thought I created document last next
one, next one, next 113.
13 internal node. Oh,
I did not create one. OK, if we go,
that's all 13, only 13 sheets.
Yeah.
OK, but you got the idea, right? History,
how it looks.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. OK, that works.
S.
You can put some examples saying like the
quantity changed for the shipment for
this order, the quantity changed, right?
You just create some mock, that's fine,
right? So then the date changed,
pickup date changed from this date to
this date, right?
Or you can say that the order number of
Mm.
orders, a new order was inserted, right?
So you can put that new order you just.
Creates a mock. That's that's fine,
but you got the idea right?
OK.
It is exactly just like how Jira.
You need to know which person did that
and when it was added. Date, time, date,
time, person and action.
Only four elements.
Date time action. OK,
but it's always registered by action,
right?
When one one person does an action is is
getting out of registered in in the
history.
Correct.
It gets registered in the history.
Say for example if something someone
changed on the order right,
it gets recorded on the.
There are like multiple attributes.
Mhm.
One of the attribute is changed.
And who made the change? The someone,
some user would have logged in correct?
That logged in user made a change so that
it should map the user the element they
changed and say they could change
multiple things in one go right?
When they go to edit they can change
multiple things at that point.
Of time. What all?
What are all the things that changed,
right? It could be wait,
it could be pick up date or it could be
location or it could be just wait, right?
We don't know.
But whatever what all that can change
happen,
we have to tell the old value to new
value, old value to new value,
old value to new value and then the time.
That's all. If instruction changed,
you added an instruction,
you would just say new instruction added.
Mm.
Yeah.
Yeah, you you will add it here,
but in the history it will say a new
instruction was added to the order.
OK,
but the structures can be added here as
well, not only in orders.
Yeah, it can be added here. True.
Oh, OK, so I need to.
I need to add that too. OK.
Yeah.
For this one you can just put in plus
mark saying that you can add you know uh.
But it is going to be complex, right?
So then are you going to open order
screen and then add instructions when you
click here?
Or is it like you're going to add it
directly into the shipments or shipments
instruction?
Well,
we are in the shipments and this is
So the question.
pointing to this order.
So here I can create a button here like
somewhere here.
Right.
But that is that is pulling in from the.
OK, yeah,
you can add it inside the shipment for
this particular order.
I'm adding an instruction. Yeah,
you can do that.
Yeah.
Um,
then we have documents where I can upload
and.
Yeah, this one we saw. This is correct.
I didn't. I don't have any issues here.
Yeah.
Yeah. Notes is internal notes. Yeah, cool.
That's right.
Then it stops.
So I put it a stop number here.
Uh, stop number here.
One pick up delivery. Fantastic.
That's it.
David told me to put P here P1 and for
delivery D, right? OK.
Uh, D Yeah.
And let's go to the big one,
which is this one.
So I was trying to separate AP total,
AR total. I did it.
I should I should improve this part
because I just put it like in columns.
But then I are after analyzing I
understand.
What is this about?
And let me show you my my this thing that
I created to understand.
To understand what's going on,
but I I just wanna confirm with you as
Good, yeah.
well.
So this is what I here is this document
shows which is a web web.
Sorry,
it's it shows everything I want to know
M.
about shipments domain. OK,
so it it's separated in different things
Yeah.
because I asked the AIA,
let me explain me exceptions,
explain me tender, explain me all this.
And I tried to put everything I had to to
understand it and my knowledge as well.
So first of all we have customer order.
So customer has it creates an order,
Yeah.
right?
And when it's created it creates a load
Correct.
as well, right? So an order equals a load.
Basically, right.
Order is a copy of the load,
but it is a record that we are managing.
Odyssey is managing and order. Sorry,
load is something that Odyssey is
Mhm.
managing.
Load and shipment is what Odyssey is
managing and customer order is like order
customer manages.
Right. Say it is their truth,
truth of information.
This is what they said they would want.
Hmm.
So you want to,
you don't want to mess with that.
You don't want to change it so that you
keep that as a record. That is order,
right?
But you create a copy and then you play
OK.
with it.
OK.
That is what is load and shipments.
OK, but load. Yeah,
so load is always is is only valid when
A copy.
we are. OK, it it's a copy.
Yeah, load is a copy of a ship order.
Oh, OK.
OK. And then.
We have a shipment created, right?
So is that a shipment?
Correct.
Who creates the shipment in the 1st place?
A user system?
System load cannot stand alone.
Load cannot stand alone by itself.
OK.
It needs a shipment.
It is something like a high level.
It's a synopsis of a load, right?
I don't want to read the load every time
because it's a lot of information.
Right.
Shipment is a more concise information,
Mhm.
right?
And a shipment can have multiple loads.
If I have 3 loads inside a shipment,
right,
I don't want to go and read 3 loads every
time. I just see the shipment.
I understand that there are three loads.
It will tell that it there are three
loads inside it.
Right.
And then it'll tell what is the origin,
what is the final destination.
OK, perfect.
Right.
Instead of thinking out of the three
loads, which is going to be the first,
which is going to be the second and which
is going to be third,
or how I need to pick up,
how I need to move,
shipment is going to define all that.
OK. Yeah. And inside a shipment,
you can have more one or more loads
because of that, right? OK.
Yeah, correct.
So when you create a shipment,
when the system creates a shipment,
you you are creating also a by shipment
and a sell shipment, right?
Parex.
OK.
And.
Which in the beginning is nothing because
it's empty and then you.
Yeah.
It it'll, it'll be in the beginning,
it'll be the same thing.
But as you start identifying a carrier,
the elements of it will change.
The cost is going to change, right?
The buy side,
you're going to have one cost because you
are buying it from the carrier,
so you're not going to sell it to the
sell it to the customer.
For the same cost,
you might right say for example there are
different models,
but forget that normally when you buy you
don't try to sell it for the same cost,
right? You do some kind of a markup.
That is why you have a sell site to
record information.
Like what is the cost you are selling the
shipment to that customer?
OK. Yeah,
because we are buying the shipment and we
are selling the shipment, right.
And then you have planning consolidation,
Correct.
so we can combine multiple loads to the.
In one shipment to reduce carriers and
lost and.
Correct.
That process happens way before, right?
Say you create a shipment and then the
Mm.
planning happens.
OK, so it's automatic in the background.
Yeah, in that background that happens.
OK. But you don't do cross,
cross like let's say cross consolidation
between customers, right?
Right now they're not doing,
but we are planning to do it.
Oh, nice. Yeah.
And then we have carrier selection.
Correct.
Planning is about carrier selection,
And.
right?
Planning is identifying a list of
carriers and out of that which carrier
you want to select.
Mhm.
So routing guide gives you a list of
carriers, right?
Mhm.
And then the tendering process finalizes.
The selection of the carrier.
OK.
So planning,
consolidation and routing guide,
it's all together, right?
It's OK if you want to understand it,
OK.
that's fine, but it's all together.
It's it's like a it's like a step
planning is imagine which all loads.
You cannot combine random loads, right?
You need.
There should be a strategy to combine.
Mm.
Find loads.
Mhm.
It's better for the carrier to
consolidate those loads, right?
It's better for the carrier to go and
pick it up.
Mm.
He spends only like 5 minutes at your
place,
then he drives another 10 minutes and
picks up another load and then both needs
to go to the same location, right?
Then or probably into a different city
Mm.
which is like again 5.
Minutes apart,
then that same carrier can do that, right?
Mhm.
So that is what is planning is about.
Which two loads can be combined?
Can it be combined or should it go
separate, right?
So that is what the planning is all about.
But depending on the planning,
the carrier is selected, right?
After the planning is done,
then the carrier selection comes.
OK.
That's where the routing guide looks into
the OK,
Yes.
you have planned these kind of loads
right together.
Mhm.
I cannot put randomly any carrier I need.
I have a logic saying that OK,
this carrier operates in this particular
route.
So he would be the better person.
But does he have the capacity to carry
right? Does he have a larger truck?
You might have a a load put together
OK.
which is like 8000 lbs,
but his truck might carry only 5000 lbs.
Mm OK.
Then it analyzes whether that routing
guide it has is a suitable routing guide
for this particular plan.
So you do a plan and then you based on
the plan you evaluate to say if you are
building your home right, what do you do?
You put a plan right and if it is going
to be a.
Huge complex, right?
If you're building your own home or it's
going to be a business site.
If it is a business site,
you want to give it to an architect or a
contractor who has experience in doing a
business site, right?
If it is a home construction,
Mhm.
then you think about I need to give it to
a contractor who has experience.
Building homes, right?
You don't give it to random people,
you evaluate.
That is what the evaluation process
happens during routing guide identifying
which are the carriers I can send it to.
OK.
And when once you send it is this there
then is when when tendering happens,
right?
Because carriers can reject or accept
ones, right?
Correct.
Yeah,
you have a list and then you now start
walking through that list.
If they say no,
you go to the next one and it's always
Next one.
trying to get the the best,
the best rank it or something, OK.
Exactly, exactly. Yeah.
You start from the best and you go to the
last preferred option.
OK, perfect.
And here is where exceptions happens,
right? Because if in tendering you don't,
you are not able to find a carrier,
that is when your system is stuck and you
need to to.
Yeah,
it is not able to decide if you can send
Oops.
it to the next carrier.
Even though the list is there,
there could be so many reasons, right?
The carrier might not have the capacity
for that day.
Sure and.
Right.
So the then it will stop and if for some
reason it says that the customer would
want to review the shipment every time
before you could tender to the next
carrier, it will stop.
There could be a condition like that,
right? It could be any condition, right?
OK.
There are like 16 conditions.
One of the condition fails, it won't,
it's not going to.
Auto tender to the next carrier.
It'll put it for user review.
8.
OK.
And that that's when our our
visualization in shipments works, right?
Because this is, this is important,
FedEx.
this one, right? Exactly.
Exactly.
That is where that is where you are and
you're trying to resolve all those.
All of those, OK.
And move it to monitoring.
You're trying to push it into monitoring,
Eh.
right?
Where monitoring is like system is
Hmm.
working so it knows what to do.
Oh yeah, let let me go there. So yeah,
system is working so.
Yeah, exactly. When, when,
when you have it, uh, working,
then it is listed here, right?
Correct.
OK and.
Then.
That is like customer is now knows the
carrier and the carrier went to their
So.
OK.
place and picked up the shipment right
and the customer is sending you an
electronic message saying the maybe you
planned 10 boxes they shipped.
11 boxes you want to record it properly.
Right. When you when you get that message,
you record what exactly they shipped.
Did they ship according to your plan or
did they ship extra or did they shipped
it to a different carrier,
whatever it could be, right?
I have.
Say you planned it for ABC,
but XYZ went there as a carrier for some
other shipment.
They mistakenly put this one on XYZ.
That could also happen.
OK.
Right. Whatever be it,
they they send that information to you
electronically.
You're capturing that information and
updating it on the shipment.
OK, yeah,
that's why you told me then this one that
I that I don't don't worry about this.
This is this is after after the.
Correct. It is. It is not there.
It's already we have developed all that
particular section.
Rating failure. OK.
And let me go to the next one. OK,
so this is basically the same, right?
The entity relationships, order load,
whatever, blah blah blah.
Correct.
Yeah, correct. Correct.
OK and exceptions and monitoring.
Yeah, data issues, correct.
These are all exception types.
OK, so this is the last time.
OK.
Gender issues. Oh yeah,
here explains the part.
You have become already an expert.
So many,
so many years we have been working,
so you captured all that.
I'm trying to.
Yeah.
It's that that's because I was working on
the weekends as well.
OK, so yeah.
No, that that is how you learn, right?
So you just spend a little bit more and
then you know what it is and then you can
take a little cool time and relax.
And because you're not scratching your
head and trying to understand what's
going on because you've done your
homework.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly. And I need to know things.
That's my nature. So that's normal for me.
Yeah, true, true.
I also work the same way, right?
And uh, yeah.
I cannot like if you if you know halfway
point and I don't understand fully,
then it puts me like in a tough spot,
right? I need to understand it more.
Oh, OK. Yes, that that is a good strategy.
Well, it's it's,
I think it's personality thing as well,
right?
Hmm, correct.
Because it's like you don't, you're not,
you're not passive enough to just say, OK,
Yeah.
it's fine. So let's go to APAR cost,
payable, receivable.
Correct.
So this is the APIAAR that I that I got
and So what I understood from our last
Correct.
call on the.
On this prototype, let me open one.
Is that inside here?
These two need to look together.
I mean like, oh, sorry,
I'm sorry about that.
Right. So we have APA.
Let me do this better. OK,
so we have all of these attributes for AP
and all of these attributes for AR and we
should be able to look.
Correct.
Costs together, right?
Not just the the the total cost.
Correct. Exactly.
Yeah, say what do you have?
Total is correct.
You also need the breakdown of it.
Yeah, sure. The breakdown. Exactly.
That that is a word. That is a word. OK.
Yeah, right. Say for example,
every load will have its own breakdown,
right? Say for example,
if you take this load right,
if you go to that other screen.
Hmm.
Right, so you have base rate, fuel,
discount, H2C, SOC, right? Stop of charge.
All this will be appearing on load one.
All this will be appearing on load 2.
All this will be appearing on load 3.
Right.
And it'll get distributed based on its
weight.
OK.
Right. Say for example,
load total weight is let's say 4000 lbs,
right?
Load one is 2000 and load 2 and load 3 is
1000 thousand.
Load one will be have a higher value.
You don't have to calculate it,
but imagine.
Right. You have just have to show that OK,
this weight is higher.
So load one cost is going to be higher
for because it is 2000 lbs and load two
cost is going to be like load two and
load three's cost is going to be the same
Mhm.
because it is.
1000 1000.
OK.
OK, got it. Sure.
Yeah, then then I need to.
Right,
the completed completed comes only after
you do the PGI.
Oh, what? So, yeah, I remember so.
No.
Only after you receive a PGI right,
you update the shipments because you
received a PGI.
PGI updates the sell side of it.
Oh, OK, yeah,
because PGI is like confirmation, right?
Correct. Yeah,
that is why it is called a completed cost.
This is the the final.
Completed is final cost.
So until that point you don't receive.
At this point you don't have a PGI,
so your completed cost will be nothing.
You don't show anything on the completed
side.
That's why I asked you to blank it out.
You show it, you just grayed out,
but now no information shows up on the.
Yeah,
you can say like you know not PGI or
something, right?
No completed cost as no PGI.
And what if we do some data that it's
that we have PGIPGR to showcase this part
as well or it's not possible it's like
because I.
Yeah, not.
It won't be under the planning phase,
right?
It will only happen on the PGI phase,
right? So say the same shipment,
same shipment someone is viewing on the
Yeah, of course. Yeah, because.
PGI, right? Say for example,
you have all this,
Hmm.
you will have a similar screen, right?
You might have.
We have to show, say for example,
we might have to develop it later,
but we we don't have to do it right now,
right? So once it is PGI,
so the all this one you're seeing right,
PGI error, all those right,
it will have its own view.
I don't know how to show that.
I sent you a link, right?
Maybe we will do it later, right?
I don't think that's link is still
working the QA link.
The QA I don't.
Where did you send it to me? I don't.
Yeah.
One second.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. The, the, the, yeah,
the platform. Yeah, I remember, yeah.
The platform, yeah,
that link is still not working for me.
Also it is showing as blank every time I
try to open right? But if you see.
No, it's, it's, it's the. Jana, it's.
Let me let me show it to you.
I I discovered a way to make it work
again. What's the name of it's QA?
Mhm.
Let me send you a QA.
Now this was all the.
OK, here it is.
It's ODM. It's in my notes. I always.
I have it. I'm gonna put it in the chat,
yeah.
Yeah, I pasted it in chat.
You can use that.
Oh.
Yeah, take all one photo.
Mm.
You go to Safari.
OK, what I did there was going incognite.
Mm.
And.
Yeah, but I did it in Chrome, I think.
Yeah, I think Chrome is better for that.
Uh.
There you go.
It's not working.
It's still not loading. Yeah,
that's right.
Let me, let me, let me log out.
Yeah, remove the dashboard. Yeah, no.
1.
Microsoft.
And then that that's the part where I
always forgot.
Yes.
OK, and it's not.
OK.
I can swear to God it was working, Jenna.
I can swear to God, Microsoft.
But it was very interesting because it
worked on a certain.
Browser.
And then it did not work on the other
ones, yeah.
Yeah, and didn't work on the other ones,
but here it is there you see.
Uh, here that works right.
So if you click on the third one,
So so try try to.
uh here you see here if you come down
right if you click on the shipments.
Oh.
Huh.
The shipments.
No,
you just click on the highlight the the
shipping number, sell shipping number,
right? Yeah. Oh,
you are on the quote entry screen,
not this one.
Um.
If you go here also you can try right
enter base rate as 1000.
Oh yeah, select USD or anything.
Any currency, that's fine. Yeah.
And then put market plus 100.
Yeah, and then select USD.
OK. Then you add some charges.
You see the markup that comes,
you see AP and AR,
so AP is 1000 and the AR is 1000 hundred,
Mhm.
right? You see that?
So that is how it calculates.
Mhm.
Then if you put some charges,
it'll be updated on both sides.
OK.
Right. Yeah. Add something 1819.
That's fine, yeah.
Mount. Ohh
Yeah, yeah, that's fine. Anything.
Right.
Do you see the charges are getting added
Mhm.
on both sides?
So this is how you enter a quote, right?
And then you save it.
You have a quote and then it it does it
spot, right?
But if you go back to the other screen,
save it, no problem. Yeah,
go to the first post PGI, PGR,
click on that box. No,
the second first one, first one.
This one.
No, sorry.
This box. Yeah, yeah.
And then click on the cell shipment ID.
Cell shipment number, right? Yeah.
Click on that. Any number. Yeah.
Click on any number. Yeah.
So this is the shipment screen, right?
So this if the user we might have to put
Mhm.
a button here to say that OK,
view my shipment and then it'll show take
them to the entire shipment that they can
see.
It'll go to that particular screen
because we it it is not a shipment view,
OK.
it is an error view, right?
The customer sent the shipment
information just telling us saying that
OK, this is what they shipped on the PGI,
but there are some errors on the file
which the user should correct before it
can apply be applied on the sell side of
the shipment.
I told you right,
a PGI is an electronic document, right?
Huh.
When the PGI comes,
there are certain errors.
Yeah.
It validates the errors.
It checks certain parameters.
Say for example, instead of LTL,
if they send Lt. right,
it is not a proper code.
System doesn't understand and you cannot
let that directly go and update your
OK.
shipment because it will cause some error.
Oh, OK.
Right, so you're catching that message,
you are validating it and then you are
letting it go and update on the sell side
of the shipment here.
Ideally what you want is you want to put
a button here to say that view my
shipments,
view my shipment and then when they click
on that shipment it go and opens the same
page.
As like what they would see in the bottom
of the screen, we need to think about it,
but right now that is why we are not
there yet.
Oh, OK.
How to get how to show the customer,
show the user the exact shipment
information right there.
The shipment is as a line, correct?
But how can we get to the user to view
the shipment information of that
particular for this particular error,
right?
You see that the cell shipment number.
If they click on the cell shipment number,
it should open the exact cell shipment
Hmm.
and then show them what are all the
details inside that cell shipment.
That is what you're constructing on the
other screen, right? 3 loads, 4 loads,
two orders.
How many orders are there right map to
that shipment?
Mm.
OK.
OK, that song sounds complicated.
So this we will work later.
Yeah this we will work later.
Once we finish that we can work later how
to take from here and put it into like
how to give that view to the user.
OK. OK.
We will not worry about that then now.
Yeah, we don't worry about it right now,
right? The PGI PGR let it remain as it is.
OK.
We just need to connect it between PGI
PGR and the shipment,
not the shipment exception screen,
not the shipment monitoring screen.
Right, but shipment detail screen, right?
We need only the bottom section if you
come down if you click on one shipment.
Right. I need this information alone.
What are all the orders inside it?
What are all the products inside it,
right? What is its cost allocation?
You go to the cost allocation.
At that point of time you will have
completed cost, right?
The completed cost will be filled.
Mhm.
Those things will start coming up.
What were the instructions for that,
right?
I need specific details of that shipment
alone. How to get that?
So an overall like information about
everything that this shipping has, OK.
That shipment has, yeah,
this entire bottom section for that
shipment should show up.
OK, basically, yeah, basically.
I should see the orders.
I should be able to see the products,
what's inside it.
I should be able to see whom it was
tendered to, the cost allocation,
the instruction, everything.
What had happened to the history of it,
right?
Just to understand if someone wants to
understand something about that shipment.
When it is in the PGI, right?
Because you might have worked very long
OK.
time back, it could be at least 15 days,
20 days and you see lot of shipments you
might not be able to remember.
So that's why we need to give them all
that so that they will be able to look
and see what are those.
Yeah,
because you lose context super easily.
There is a lot of information and as a
user you you probably forget what you
Yeah.
Correct, correct.
were doing before. OK, let's go. OK,
so we are clear on this.
And OK, this is my data model,
how I am handling data in this in this
demo.
So maybe I can send you a screenshot but
Mm.
if you can read it like the main table
row for example has has this.
By shipment. Yeah, correct. Correct. Yeah,
that is right. Scac,
all these correct order tab.
Order tab will have order details,
whatever you have under the order section.
That's why I told you, right.
We don't have to construct it.
We just have to plug the information from
the order screen because there are
different tabs within the order.
I just start use certain sections and
show that inside the order tab.
Yeah.
For each of those orders, right?
So that is just an idea for me to say
OK.
Huh.
like, OK,
these are all the this one we want to
show.
But what we I wanted to do is you are
already constructing the order right?
Within that order you will have different
sections. You have the header section,
then you will have the general section or
the you know.
What is that called consigner,
consignee section, then bill to section,
then you will have product section,
then you will have instruction section,
then you will have additional accessorial
section.
So many sections are there within the
order.
So which section is more important for?
For me inside a shipment,
I just want to bring those directly from
order and display it here.
OK.
OK, sure.
You mean display it in in our in our
shipments, right? Yeah.
Direct in our shipments in the bottom
section.
OK, here, right?
Right. You have. Yeah, that is the one,
correct.
OK, OK then the other tab. OK,
so maybe I need to complete this because
this looks very like uncompleted.
OK, so then this stop stop.
Correct.
So yeah, so this.
Product tab, routing, whatever you have,
you have the entire data model, yeah.
Yeah, um, obviously I took this from.
Instead of calling all this data model
right,
say for example many of these are
repeated.
Your data model if you look like it'll be
a say for example load model,
load data model right?
Then you will have within that load.
What are all the fields relevant to that
load?
Then you'll have shipment data model.
Within that shipment there will be only
certain fields. As I told you,
shipment is a summary of the load, right?
Then what are all those?
Then you'll have an order data model,
right?
So what are all the order and what are
all the fields related to that?
Then you you will call it a star.
Stop and stop will have an overlap
between,
say it'll call the customer information,
it'll call the order information,
and then it'll have certain information
by itself, right?
Say for example the pickup date,
delivery date, stop.
What is the exact stop for that?
OK, uh, yeah.
Yeah, but your idea is correct.
This is how it will work.
So basically what I understand from that
is that all of this data is the same.
Probably we have a bigger collection of
data,
just that some parts are using some of
that data,
Exactly.
other parts are using some of that data,
but all of them are OK.
Yeah, correct. Correct. Correct.
You're right.
So the work here for our product for our
demo or and also for the the real real
software is that how we can use how we
can relate that data for each instance of
for example here right.
Yeah.
Instance of a usage.
Correct.
So you have that that wire,
you have the the complete data wired
That is what.
already in some way and and maybe it's in
Jira and company, OK.
Yeah.
Yeah, there is.
There is a confluence page and they are
managing it. If you want a link,
I can get it right.
Or place. If you have it, I can.
I don't directly have it,
but I can find one,
but it might not be up to date, right?
So I will ask a guy.
I know a data modeler is there, right?
He's managing all that. I'll ask him,
I'll put it in a chat and then add you
right as saying that can you share the
latest data model link and then he will
share that link and then.
OK.
Then you can use it.
Yeah, perfect. That will be great. Uh,
so I can improve this one because this is
Yeah.
my guesswork, you know,
it's because of what I from what I see
Correct. Correct. Yeah. Yeah.
and then.
Oh no, this is not. Then I have questions.
I think we we already did this,
the API cost breakdown and then the
Yeah, yeah.
history versus versus history.
We did that spot the process.
Yeah, spot bid is a separate, right?
Spot bid is a overflow board, right?
Say for example,
you exhausted all the tender,
all the carriers for that the routing
guide gave you, right?
None of the carriers accepted it.
Right.
Then what do you do is you you have
OK.
another specific different set of
carriers.
Right to whom you will be sending this
information to.
Mm-hmm.
Mhm.
Right,
because you need a carrier for this
particular shipment.
So you would send it to a different set
of carriers.
And what do you do is it's like a tender,
right?
How do you say if you the information
will be posted to all the carriers at one
time, right? And you set a time.
Saying that within 60 minutes it says
yeah,
within 60 minutes you need to send me
this information.
Mhm.
Yeah,
within 60 minutes you need to send me
whether what is your code.
You saw the other process right code
where we did earlier.
Yeah.
Right. So they will give you a base rate,
then they will do markup and then you can
add charges, right.
So all that similar things the carrier
will send you right saying, oh,
this is my base rate,
this is my fuel charge,
this is my stop off charge and they will
give the breakdown and then send it to
Odyssey.
Odyssey will use that and identify.
They have a mechanism. Again,
there is a mechanism to identify saying
that OK,
this is like I'm going to identify out of
6 carriers it sent.
4th carrier is the best carrier because
he he charged.
His quote was less and I know that he's a
good carrier,
so it'll award that spot bid to that
carrier.
Spot means what you're going and shopping.
It is not a contracted rate.
You're going and shopping in the market
to find a carrier and at one time you're
getting quotes from everyone.
So you start the meeting.
That is what the spot bid process.
Yeah correct.
You start a bid process and then you
start the bid process and you end the bid
process.
Within that process time you can get a
code and you validate the code and get
one right. That is what the bid process.
But we have not gone to that yet so I've
not created screens so.
OK, OK, so it's now.
That's a separate one.
That will that will start after the
tender process, right?
You exhausted every tender and you don't
know where to go, right?
And then that's the final final option
where you can search for a carrier.
Oh, I see. OK,
so probably will look similar from the
tender in UI as well.
Correct. It is similar to tender screen.
Yeah, it is similar to tender screen,
OK.
but it is like it is a simple one
screener only, right? You click the,
it'll make a call,
it'll identify a carrier and then say
that OK,
you put a timer on it and then you post
Um.
it. That's all you post it to an external.
Yeah.
Board, but you won't.
You won't see that we don't have to
design the external,
but you will design it.
I won't have to design it because there
is a Kathleen's team who will be working
on that portal.
Alright, carrier portal.
It'll go to the carrier portal where the
OK.
carrier will be logging into that portal
and then submitting a quote like just
like how you submitted a quote earlier,
they will be doing that in their carrier
portal.
Catch. Perfect.
Yeah, yeah, it's a little more complex,
but I'm, you know,
we will get to that point when we once we
finish all this.
OK, yeah, sure. That is,
that is is is getting wider and wider.
We should not get that fairly fast.
See, imagine they built,
they built this 125 years, right?
So we are trying to do it in one year.
Wow, that's. And I have a question.
Steve is is like he knows like the system
from a long time ago as well, right?
It seems like a person that knows a lot.
Dave. Steve. Not Steve. Not Steve. Dave.
Dave. Oh, Dave.
So Dave is is here longer than anyone,
Yeah, Dave Schultz, not David.
Dave Schultz.
maybe.
Uh, Dave Schultz. Dave Schultz.
OK Oh yeah,
he wrote an e-mail the other day.
I saw a reference. OK.
Yeah, yeah.
So he is a guy who knows everything.
4.
Most of it, right?
He might not know net net and certain
things,
but he he and there is another guy called
Doug, right?
So both of them worked with Odyssey for a
very long time,
2025 years and they they are like
******** programmers and as they were
working in that system for so long they.
Know about this concept as well.
Oh, so they. Yeah. So Odyssey,
we're hiring software developers as well
in there.
For for building their own things, right?
Right, right.
So he built the currently the system TMS
system is all do exist, right.
So we are extracting the things from TMS
OK.
system and then we are developing a new
system.
All this process exists,
but it exists in a different way.
OK, cool.
It is not exactly the same,
but it's somewhat similar.
OK, gotcha. Let's go with the next one.
So action buttons,
the ones that you showed me in your.
Action button for PowerPoint. Yeah,
it's in the second PowerPoint if I go
PowerPoint, right?
back there.
OK, I can't handle many things,
many software things,
but I cannot handle PowerPoint,
so it's the opposite to you.
Yeah, there you go. This actions, right?
Yeah, yeah, these are actions for options,
right? As I told you,
a carrier can you when you want to select
the carrier and then you want to tender,
say for example I don't want the system
to tender to the first carrier,
you select the you'd see a checkbox near
to the second line.
Hmm, care. No.
No, no. Bottom options, options,
options are carriers, right? Yeah, bottom,
second, second line. Yeah.
So on the first, yeah,
Just a second.
you have the checkbox on the left side,
left, left, left.
Left. Yeah,
you can select that and then it'll check
Oh, OK.
and then you can tender.
You click on the action button tender.
So what it'll do is OK, it'll not wait.
Say for example the current date on it is
what you know, I cannot read it too small.
It's February.
221, right? Say 221,
Say imagine you are two one. Yeah,
you are like a 210, right? 2/10/2026,
right?
You don't want it to wait until 221 to
start the tender,
but you want to send the tender now
itself,
but you don't want it to send it to the
first carrier, right?
You click on the second.
Areas the check box that you have
highlighted and then you click on tender.
OK.
Right. You are skipping the system.
You're telling you're not.
Oh, I see.
You're you're overriding the system,
right?
You are and you starting it earlier.
System can only start maybe like 3 days
before the pickup date.
The pickup date here is what?
Uh.
223, right?
So the system can start tendering.
Imagine there is a rule.
Systems can start tendering 220.
It cannot do it 219.
It cannot do 218 or 217, right?
It can start only 220.
Hmm.
That's how it has been set up, right?
It could be 3 days,
it could be 4 days for some customers.
So there are some time.
Within which it can start tendering and
it should start tendering by that date,
Mm.
right? So if you want to override it,
so if you are in 210 but you don't want
OK.
to wait for the system to start by itself,
right then you can have multiple options.
You don't want to go to the first one,
but you you want to go with second one,
then you check here and say.
Tender.
OK.
Right. So then you didn't.
Suddenly you made a you you made a
decision not to tender to this carrier.
You can go and say cancel.
Oh, OK.
Right, that is why you need a cancel.
OK,
but here is I think something will be
showing here that it's already tendering
so I can cancel it.
Yeah, it's tender status.
Tender status is there, right?
You see the tender status, the AP cost.
After the AP cost,
Mm.
you see the tender status. Yeah,
it says sent, right? If you canceled it,
Oh, here. Oh.
it'll say cancel.
OK.
Say as as the second one did not even
start, so you don't have a status at all.
Yeah, sure, it's empty.
Yeah,
it's empty because you didn't do anything
to it, right?
Because the first one is sent.
OK.
If you have the second one as sent,
the first one would be like declined or
it could be cancelled.
Huh.
Right.
If the system had done it automatically,
OK.
right,
it would always do to the first one
because you see the second column,
it's a ranked #1.
Yeah. Uh, they're ranking. OK, Yeah. OK.
Right.
Yeah,
so that is the best option you can send
it to right now.
That's why the system will automatically
order it by certain way,
saying like rank one, rank two,
rank three, right?
OK,
so you can also cancel whatever the
system actually sent it to, right?
Correct. You need to cancel that,
override the system.
You cannot just accept everything, right?
So you need to override it at cell
sometimes.
Maybe the carrier did send a message,
cancellation message,
but we did not reach our system.
There was an error, right?
And there was system was down.
Um.
How would you do it?
You need to do it from here, right?
So that is why you you either you will
OK.
say like oh the carrier declined it and
then you go and check and say decline and
then you put a note saying carrier called
and said like decline because they don't
have the truck was down or truck was you
know they did not have the spag truck
something.
Whatever could be the reason.
OK, OK, cool. That's cool. Let's go.
Let's go back to the store.
So let me see the question again.
It says you mentioned action buttons
should change depending on which tab
we're on.
And.
Yeah, I I think, well,
I I understand that part,
but here we said the other the way this
actions is important, right?
For example to sorry the the button here
in the right, the actions drop down.
Which one?
One second. Let me see. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. Actions, right. Correct.
We we will have a the the this is for
your second.
So this is for all all all of this is for
monitoring right the the ones that you
Yes.
Correct.
explain it to me.
So we are still on the exception so.
Um,
here it says actions by shipment edits.
Yeah, it's like by shipment edit.
Then you should be able to select
multiple shipments and then mark it for
tendering.
Say for example everything is like OK,
but you need to I I maybe you can just
add it as saying.
Tender to the preferred carrier as one of
the option.
OK.
Tender to preferred carrier, right?
Preferred carrier is always the first
carrier.
Yeah, OK.
Because the rank one is your preferred,
right?
So that is why you call it the preferred
carrier.
So this is similar to the other one that
you explained me, right?
You're correct. Exactly.
OK, cool. Um, let's go to.
So it says you mentioned action.
Can you specify options for the tailoring?
Consolidation visibility.
What is that when load?
Uh.
Where loads are consolidated and.
OK,
should the user see which load were
combined? OK,
if there is a visual indicator in the
main table showing the shipment,
it has the orders which.
It says that it's combined right.
David did not want that information to
the user saying which are those loads
related to that order, right?
Mhm.
So that is where the orders.
Will have its own loads.
When you go to the order screen, not here,
but in the order domain, right? It will.
It should show this order has this load
in the order domain, right? Not here,
so that's fine.
Yeah, mhm.
OK.
That is why we are not putting the load
number anywhere on that screen,
because he doesn't want to tell the users
that the actual Odyssey users that there
is a load for the shipment.
They should think only about shipments,
right? They should not think about loads.
That is what is the idea.
Is because shipment is what they are
trying to find a carrier for.
OK.
It's not the loads that they are trying
to find a carrier.
Oh, OK, cool.
And then direct cost of usage.
Yeah, direct cost usage. Yeah,
it's like how much of saving you,
And it says.
you had a margin, right? You see there.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can add one more, right?
Direct cost saving and margin.
Margin is between buy and sell and direct
cost saving is how much they saved.
Like if it has been shipped separately,
right? If it just went by itself,
what will be the cost?
And if it went along in a consolidation,
right?
Went with another load.
What is the saving for it?
So here you have the margin, right?
If you go back to your screen, yeah,
Mhm.
this margin is between the buy and the
sell at the AP and the AR cost, correct.
Mhm.
Uh.
There should be one more, right? Oh,
one more to add saying.
You have a where you have a direct cost.
You don't have a direct cost.
You can put a direct cost and say that
what is the saving? OK,
you cannot say on the shipment because
shipment will not have its direct cost.
Only the order will have its direct cost.
You see that order has a direct cost.
Very. I think it's here. Oh, here. Yeah.
Huh.
Right. Yeah.
Order has its own direct cost, right?
Then you have the customer cost, right?
That is the AR cost.
OK. And there.
You see that if the yeah direct cost and
AR cost right.
In this case it is it is showing like
that.
But what it should ideally show is your
direct cost was 1000 and the AR cost was
800 right? Because of that you save 200.
If you had shipped directly you would
have speed more.
Because you're combining with us and
shipping, you're saving some money.
Exactly. Consolidation safe, safe money,
right?
That's that's the idea behind.
Yeah, exactly.
OK, OK and and it says.
This is some somewhere we need to bring
that one out in there, right?
Uh, yes.
So direct cost is there.
So if a direct cost we have already got
OK.
the direct cost in,
what is the savings the customer is
getting out of this?
Consolidation, right?
So every order should have cost savings,
Mhm.
right? Cost saving, direct cost saving,
right?
And then add a difference between the AR
cost amount for the order minus the.
Direct cost, right?
That will be the saving amount.
Mhm.
OK.
And then finally PGIPGR trigger for
completed cost.
And oh, you already explained this, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah. OK. Well, I think that's it.
That's cool.
You you learned everything almost like
Oh.
90% of it. Only thing is overflow,
overflow and a little bit of PGI.
I know it's.
Exactly. I mean, I'm still,
I'm still like forgetting things.
Like I write things sometimes and then I
forget because I'm not used to it yet.
Correct, correct, correct.
But little by little, yeah, OK,
so let me stop sharing this.
Yeah, this is this is complex, right?
It's not like you create some website.
It's not like that because website you
can, it's all like static, right?
You can put some information.
That information is not exactly relevant
to the next page.
It's more like an information where
you're storing,
but this one is like every.
The information has some kind of a rule
behind it,
and it drives certain other information.
Mhm.
Yeah, yeah, of course it's not.
It's not the same as a website, of course.
Correct. That is what it is.
That's why it makes it more complex and
OK.
uh, you know,
that's what makes it more interesting as
well.
Yeah, I think it's interesting.
I kind of like it actually. I was really.
Yeah.
I didn't like my my last job, for example,
because it was more a lot about
animations and stuff and I was kind of
tired that it was that it it wasn't like
Hmm.
about.
Information that is true or false, right?
Because in this business you are,
you're true or false,
you want to save money,
you want to do like specific stuff.
But then creativity is more like what's
Pedicts.
what's the perception of the of the of
the boss. You know, if the boss likes it.
Then it's good then and I don't like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This one is like you have.
We are always thinking in terms of
persona, right? The user persona,
how they are going to see this,
who is going to use it? Say for example,
the first couple of screens,
the planner is going to use it, right?
Yeah, sure.
If the planner is going to use it,
the same screens at some point of a time,
the accountants or audit team will use it,
right? The shipment screen,
Mm.
once it is all done, PGI is done.
They want to see what is the cost,
what was that we had it on the carrier
cost. Carrier would send an invoice,
but they would want to see what was the
rate that we.
Discussed with the carrier, right?
Then they will go into the shipment and
see their AP cost.
See it'll have a different perspective at
the point of time.
Exactly. And we need to, as you said,
we need to create the those users
personas as well and do the the users
actually OK.
Exactly right. Yeah.
Right now the persona is only the
planners, right?
The planner is how they are working.
That is what we are thinking in terms of
them and then we are doing.
But ideally in in our projects as well,
we normally create the personas.
But you know,
we didn't have people at the time when it
all started and started.
Started working so we didn't create all
that persona.
Mm.
But the persona is the say there are a
couple of people who actually use these
screens, right?
The audit team will use the screen.
Then that is why you need history.
What changed? What time, right?
And what is that they are interested.
We have to ask those questions to them
saying like, OK.
What is that important to you?
What is that you're looking at?
And then we need to connect all that into
the product, right? But I don't,
Mhm.
I don't think we all did that,
but we have some kind of an understanding
of what is important and that is why we
trying to put all those things in.
Yeah,
I think at a certain point it will be a
good,
a good idea to to approach to those
people,
to those end users and try to try to like
Yeah.
have their feedback on based on what we
are done, we were done already so.
Exactly, exactly, exactly.
So we don't, we don't deliver. Yeah,
some things like, OK, oh.
That is why we are doing this right.
So once you have this prototype,
we are going to take it to the business
and going to tell them saying that this
Mhm.
is how ideally you will be working.
Mm-hmm. Exactly. Now we need this part,
you know, or.
Right. If you,
if you complete the what is that the
tendering part, right,
that's where we will then take it to them
and then we will show them and but it's
coming out really well.
It's like it gives them a very good idea,
right,
saying how it works and what happens when
you do this.
Yeah.
So it gives them a pretty good idea.
So if you complete the small,
small open items, right,
say for example the mainly the tender
page,
then I think it should be kind of OK.
Mhm.
OK, OK, John, shall we connect on Friday?
Maybe to I'm gonna update this and maybe
on Friday I can show you a hopefully a
finalized version like a beta version for
the.
Yeah, absolutely.
The demo and if it's fine,
we can launch it and if it's not,
we can we can do it again on Monday,
another Monday, something like that, OK.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We can take it to next week itself.
We can start taking it to the users and
start, you know, doing it.
But once you give that,
at least this version is kind of OK.
We can give them an idea and tell them
what it is, right?
Yeah.
OK, that sounds.
Did you have you have you already
discussed with the team on orders like
order pages and have you reviewed those?
Yeah, sure.
I know something about order and well,
So have you have you already reviewed it
with the business folks?
it's not.
Do you know that Efrain or others have
reviewed?
Yeah, yeah.
Exactly. Well,
Efrain is more in charge of that.
He's reviewing it,
but he he had the review yesterday,
if I'm not wrong,
and he had some problems because and
there were a lot of like feedback with
the business.
And that changes a lot of ideas.
So he was worried because he said so I
could not deliver this to development
because they have so many new concepts
that I wasn't aware of like they nobody
told him.
So he's like trying to figure that out
and trying to.
Business to respond some of the questions
before before pushing forward.
That's what I know.
I still need to see the.
Like the the the the like the meeting
they had. But yeah,
Yeah.
basically that's that was that was the
the feedback like there are another
requirements that David didn't tell him
or Caitlin.
Correct, correct, correct.
At the at the time, yeah. So I I don't,
I I don't know. Like,
it's too much like to follow everything
at one at a time, yeah.
I get it. Yeah, yeah, no problem. Yeah.
But I think, yeah,
we that's why I'm saying right, the more,
the faster we are able to get it to the
Yeah.
business folks and get their feedback.
You know,
we would know where we stand until then.
See, at least the idea wise,
Yeah.
I know the concept wise is very pretty
much what they're doing.
Doing right so that we know,
but how they would want to navigate is
the question, right?
Then we can tweak it and do it.
Sure. Yeah, it's, it's,
it's good to do it fast. Yeah.
Eric.
And we have and we can have another
session with them right before, OK.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So we once you get it done right,
I can quickly once we are kind of aligned
on how it needs to look like, right,
we say that's why I'm saying you can give
some functionality and then you don't
Mhm.
have to go deeper.
We can say that you can set it up and
this will come more in detail,
but this is an.
What do you say? For example,
if they wanted to change the columns,
you just put a wheel and say that you can
change the column, right? You click on it,
you show some template and saying like OK,
you change the column by moving it, right?
So you don't have to explain this is how
the functionality would work,
but you can just say like OK,
this is how you can arrange,
but it's not a final version,
it's just some.
Animation to get you give you an idea,
right?
So you you just have to first level cut.
It just have to give them an idea like oh
Mhm.
I I will be able to move the columns,
I will be able to adjust my columns.
So that's that's all their understanding
should be right.
Then as we go deeper you can start
refining.
Once you get the feedback you can start
refining.
This is a better idea based on the
feedback and then we can connect again
some point later and this is how we would
want the setting to be right column
setting and then we can tell them this is
one example. Do you like it right?
And then we can use the same kind of
approach for every setting.
Mhm.
OK, yeah,
it can be reusable for different things.
Yeah, ideally it should be reusable,
right?
It should not be different in different
domains. It should be the same.
The idea concept should be the same in
the platform across all domains, right?
If you do a search in a particular way in
one domain,
OK.
it should be the same way you do the
search in the other domain.
Right, it cannot be like I do, uh,
natural language search in one domain and
then I need to do a filter action on the
other domain, right?
Yeah.
It should not be like that.
Yeah,
that's what too smart worries me some
things and that's why we hold the the the
global search idea. So yeah.
Correct.
You just that's why even what we are
doing, right? We are.
We can just say that we are planning on
natural language search,
but we are just working on that idea.
But you would search in this way.
We'll come back and go deeper on saying
how it'll be done right once we have a
refinement.
OK.
But this is just to give them an idea,
right? You can search.
Once you customize your search then you
can save it.
You click on the save then it brings you
a different screen.
Mm-hmm. OK.
Uh.
OK.
OK, John, I am tired. Let's uh.
Yeah, I know. It's been a long,
long marathon call.
Yeah.
It's been like we started what, 430-430,
right? Eastern. Yeah, two hours.
Yeah, it's like 2 hours later.
Could you send me the could you up?
No, three hours. We went three hours.
Three hours. Yeah, yeah, it's a lot.
Could you send me? Oh, sorry, not send me,
but like,
give me permissions for the again for the
transcripts, please after this.
Oh, sure, sure. Yeah, yeah,
I'll give you permission. No problem.
Um.
OK. Thank you, Jana. See you.
See you Friday.
Thank you. Yeah, yeah.
Talk to you tomorrow. Bye.